[{"question": " hey you guys?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " i know it&#146;s last minute, but we decided to have a halloween party.", "answer": " oh good!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " and everybody has to wear costumes.  come on! it&#146;ll be fun!", "answer": " well, i&#146;ll-i&#146;ll be there. i mean i have to wear a costume to all my classes that day anyway so&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " please tell me you&#146;re not gonna dress up like a dinosaur.", "answer": "  not two years in a row.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " look, i&#146;ll come to the party but i&#146;m not dressing up.", "answer": " you have to!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " no way! look, halloween is so stupid! dressing up, pretending to be someone you&#146;re not&#133;", "answer": " you&#146;re an actor!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " so ross, are you gonna bring mona?", "answer": " yeah. yeah, i think i will.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " that hot girl from their wedding?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " well hey-hey if she needs any idea for costumes, she could be a bikini model, or a slutty nurse, or a sexy cheerleader huh&#151;ooh-ooh, leatherface from the texas chainsaw massacre&#151;no-no-no! slutty leatherface.", "answer": " now wasn&#146;t joey hitting on her at the wedding too?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " ursula!  wait! err-err, it&#146;s me! phoebe!", "answer": " oh, i thought there was a mirror there. okay, bye-bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " wait a second! so, what&#146;s new with you?", "answer": " umm, nothing. i mean, i&#146;m getting married next week.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " yeah! yeah, it&#146;s gonna be a small ceremony. just family.  his.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " wait! if umm, if you want to come, i guess that&#146;d be okay.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " sure! why not? you could be my sister for the day.", "answer": " yeah. okay. umm, y&#146;know, my friends are having a halloween party tonight at my old apartment so, you could come. maybe i could meet the guy you&#146;re marrying.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " huh. well, i&#146;m supposed to be working at the restaurant tonight. i&#146;m supposed to be working right now, so who cares.", "answer": " by the way, it&#146;s a costume party.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " wait! you&#146;re supposed to wear a costume!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " i am! i am a woman who spent a lot of money on a dress and she wants to wear it, because soon she won&#146;t be able to fit into it.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " ahh!", "answer": " i&#146;m catwoman, who wants to borrow the dress when you&#146;re too big for it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " trick or treat!", "answer": " oh! oh! can i give out the candy? i really want to be with the kids right now. y&#146;know, ever since i got pregnant i-i have the strongest maternal instincts.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " trick or treat!!", "answer": "  just a minute!!!  look at you guys! wow! you are a very scary witch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " and you are a very funny clown.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": "  and you are so in style right now. y&#146;know, i work at ralph lauren and the whole fall line has got this like equestrian theme going on. i don&#146;t suppose you saw the cover of british vogue, but&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": "  can i just have the candy?", "answer": " yeah. sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " ah, catwoman. so we meet again.", "answer": " so we do supergirl.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " no, it&#146;s me. phoebe!", "answer": "  monica! can i talk to you for a second? listen, i appreciate you getting me the costume&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": "  oh, you did this to him?", "answer": " what?! i thought he&#146;d love it! his favorite kid's book was the velveteen rabbit!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " the velveteen rabbit was brown and white!", "answer": " well, it was either a pink bunny or no bunny at all.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " no bunny at all!! always no bunny at all!!!", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " you didn&#146;t dress up either?!", "answer": " yes i did! i&#146;m chandler.  dude, what happened?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " how is that me?", "answer": " okay. i&#146;m chandler", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": "  that is so you!", "answer": " when have i ever done that?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " trick or treat!", "answer": " oh!  well you&#146;re just the prettiest ballerina i&#146;ve ever seen.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " oh wow! that deserves another piece of candy.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " well, i have to say that earns tutu pieces of candy.", "answer": " i love you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " ohh&#133; oh, honey here. take it all.  monica! we need more candy?", "answer": " what?! there&#146;s only been like four kids.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " yeah i know, but one of them just said that she loved me so i just gave her everything.", "answer": " no wonder your pregnant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " what are you supposed to be?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " remember the russian satellite, sputnik?  well, i&#146;m a potato or a&#133;spud. and these are my antennae.  so sputnik, becomes&#133;  spud-nik. spudnik!", "answer": " wow! i don&#146;t have the worst costume anymore!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": "  hey all right, ross came as doody.", "answer": " no, i-i&#146;m not doody.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " aren&#146;t you gonna give me a kiss?", "answer": " okay, i will. but right after you tell me who the hell you are.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " ursula?", "answer": " ursula&#146;s fianc\u008fe?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " oh my god, you&#146;re the sister!", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " okay, i just slapped my future sister-in-law&#146;s ass.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " i&#146;m an idiot. uh, is your mother here? maybe i can give her a little slap on the butt.", "answer": " my mother killed herself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " she, now i knew that and&#133;now i&#146;m sweating. look at me, i&#146;m really sweating&#151;now i&#146;m saying, &quot;look at me,&quot; i&#146;m getting even sweatier. i think i probably should go.", "answer": " no-no! that&#146;s okay, we&#146;ll just start over. okay? hi! i&#146;m phoebe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " why are you looking at me like that?", "answer": " &#145;cause the sweat&#146;s getting in my eyes and its burning.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " okay.  so, what are you?", "answer": " i don&#146;t think they have a name for it. it&#146;s just i get nervous; i start sweating like crazy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": "  no i-i meant your costume.", "answer": " oh umm, i&#146;m the solar system.  yeah, my students helped me make it&#151;i teach the second grade.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " i love the second grade!", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " yeah! it&#146;s so much better than first grade when you don&#146;t know what&#146;s going on and definitely better than third grade. y&#146;know with all the politics and mind games.", "answer": " so what do you do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " y&#146;know you don&#146;t have to stand here with me, believe me&#133;", "answer": " no i&#146;m having fun. i&#146;m really&#151;and i&#146;m really-really excited for you and ursula.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " oh i feel very lucky, she&#146;s great. i think she&#146;s the most beautiful woman i&#146;ve ever seen.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " hey joey?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " you read comic books right?", "answer": " exclusively.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " who do you think would win in a fight, catwoman or supergirl?", "answer": " catwoman, hands down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " yeah&#133;", "answer": " but between you and phoebe, i&#146;d have to give the edge to phoebe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " what?! really?!", "answer": " are you kiddin&#146;? phoebe lived on the street. okay? plus, she&#146;s got this crazy temper. she&#151;she&#146;s not standing right behind me is she?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " no you&#146;re fine.  all right well, do you think i could take rachel?", "answer": " i&#146;m not sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " what?! come on i am tough! punch me right here!  as hard as you can!", "answer": " will you relax?! what are you taking this so seriously for? it doesn&#146;t matter.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " oh really? okay? well what would you say if i told you that, y&#146;know, ross or chandler could beat you up?", "answer": " i would say, &quot;woman, please!&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  hey. ursula&#146;s fianc\u008fe is really sweet! he&#146;s a teacher, he does all this volunteer work. y&#146;know normally y&#146;know, i don&#146;t like really sweaty guys. but this one? i could just mop him up!", "answer": " oh my god, phoebe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " you&#146;re getting a crush on your sister&#146;s fianc\u008fe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " no i&#146;m not! you are!", "answer": "  here comes the temper.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " trick or treat!", "answer": " hi! y&#146;know what honey, we&#146;re actually out of candy right now. but someone just went out to get some and i have been giving out money but i&#146;m out of that too. hey, can i write you a check?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": " okay, what&#146;s your name?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " lelani mayolanofavich.", "answer": " okay, i&#146;m just gonna write this out to cash.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": "  hi!", "answer": " hey mona!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " oh! hi!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " joey&#146;s gonna be thrilled! he was hoping you&#146;d come by as a slutty nurse.", "answer": " umm, actually i&#146;m just a nurse.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " you&#146;d think that would embarrass me, but you see i&#146;m maxed out.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " you made it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " wait-wait! you&#146;re umm, you&#146;re a potato&#133;", "answer": " well, i&#146;m a spud&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " and the antennae&#133;oh my god you&#146;re spudnik!", "answer": " yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " okay, here&#146;s a good one for ya. who do think would win in a fight between ross and chandler.", "answer": " i can&#146;t answer that! chandler&#146;s my husband.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " so ross?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " hey beautiful.", "answer": " hello handsome.  oh god.  oh look at you two. so when did you guys meet?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " two weeks ago.", "answer": " two weeks? that&#146;s it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " yeah, i know it sounds crazy, and it&#146;s not like me to do something so impulsive, but she&#146;s just so perfect, and we have so much in common.", "answer": " oh really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " we&#146;re both teachers.", "answer": " huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " and we were both in the peace corps.", "answer": " peace corps, really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " in fact when we were building houses in uruguay, we were, we were just two towns apart and we never met.", "answer": " yeah. it wasn&#146;t a town when i got there, but it was a town when i left.  shall we get me really drunk?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " howdy doody.", "answer": " that&#146;s funny. yeah. y&#146;know you&#146;re the funniest man here in a pink bunny costume his wife made him wear.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " oh relax man, relax. you&#146;re looking a little flushed.", "answer": "  hey-hey-hey, i think we might find out the answer to our question.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " what question?", "answer": " monica and i were talking about who could kick whose ass in a fight, you or ross?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " there&#146;s no question.", "answer": " so you think ross too?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": "  you picked ross?!", "answer": " ross is really strong! okay, he&#146;s the strongest out of all three of you!  except for joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " i cannot believe you didn&#146;t pick me.", "answer": " uh, in her defense, she&#146;s right. i am stronger. i would destroy you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " wait-wait!! okay, stop it! stop it! stop!  now listen, no one&#146;s gonna fight in this apartment.", "answer": " hey monica!  people came to see a fight, let&#146;s give &#145;em what they came for!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " hey, you guys could arm wrestle.", "answer": " yeah. listen to the slutty nurse.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": "  you&#146;re going down.", "answer": " oh yeah? you&#146;re going further down! downtown!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " oh gunther! you brought candy! thank you so much for picking this up! you are so sweet.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " trick or treat!", "answer": " gotta go!  hi! wow! there you go!  boy in the cape: my friend lewis told me you were giving out money.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " oh yeah, we were but umm, now we&#146;ve got candy. boy in the cape: i&#146;d rather have the money.", "answer": " well, that-that&#146;s not your choice. happy halloween! boy in the cape: this isn&#146;t fair.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " well is it fair that all you did was put on a cape and i gotta give you free stuff? boy in the cape: shut up!", "answer": " you shut up!  boy in the cape: you can&#146;t tell me to shut up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " uh, i think i just did. and uh-oh, here it comes again. shut up!", "answer": " rach?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": "  look honey, you don&#146;t have to do this, okay? it&#146;s the strength you have inside that means the most to me. you&#146;re loyal, you&#146;re honest, and you have integrity! that&#146;s the kind of strength that i want in the man that i love!", "answer": " that means nothing to me.  come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " hi liar!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " y&#146;know the only reason he&#146;s marrying you is because he thinks all the things you were saying about yourself were true.", "answer": " well they could be true.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " but they&#146;re not!", "answer": " yeah, it&#146;s a fine line huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " why are you lying to him?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know. he said he did all this stuff and then i said i did it too and he got so excited, it was really fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": "  honey?", "answer": "  it&#146;s a filthy, disgusting habit and i want you to quit now!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " she&#146;s helped so many people to quit smoking.", "answer": " y&#146;know, we&#146;d really better get going.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " oh right, you&#146;ve got a church group meeting tonight.", "answer": " right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": "  well, it was nice meeting you.", "answer": " you too. and ursula?! it was really nice meeting you tonight!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": "  pheebs come on! bunny vs. doody! we&#146;re waiting!   okay. okay guys, one match, winner take all.  oh wait-wait! what does the winner get?", "answer": " pride.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " and dignity.", "answer": "  okay, if you say so. all right, ready? set! go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": "  wow! they&#146;re both really strong.", "answer": " or equally weak.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": "  oh god!", "answer": " hmm?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": "  so, you gettin&#146; tired?", "answer": " nope! i can do this all day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " yeah? me too.  gettin&#146; a little tired though.", "answer": " god, i&#146;m exhausted.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " look this is starting to look really bad for me. okay? mona, mona&#146;s standing right over there.  oh god, she&#146;s talking to joey! you gotta let me win!", "answer": " no way! if anything you&#146;ve gotta let me win! my wife thinks i&#146;m a wimp!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " hey, at least you have a wife! i-i keep getting divorces and knockin&#146; people up! and i&#146;m dressed as doody.", "answer": " you&#146;re spudnik.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " come on, who are we kidding? i&#146;m doody. please? she&#146;s watchin&#146;.", "answer": " fine.  oh no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": "  oh yeah!", "answer": "  yay! my hero!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": "  you&#146;re a weird lady.", "answer": "  hey. ursula said she left her purse.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": "  what a relief. it has all the numbers of the people in her prayer chain.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " sure it does. yeah, yeah.", "answer": " well, i guess i&#146;ll see you at the wedding.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " umm listen, i don&#146;t think&#133;i don&#146;t think i&#146;m gonna make it to the wedding. so i just want to wish you all the luck in the world.", "answer": " i think we&#146;ll be okay. besides it&#146;s so perfect and  she&#146;s been saving herself for me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " okay i can&#146;t let you do this! she&#146;s lying to you.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " she is lying! and i bet i can prove it. excuse me.  okay. okay. yeah&#151;not a prayer chain, but what looks like a detailed drawing of a bank floor plan.  okay, here&#146;s the nametag from the restaurant where she works as a waitress! not a teacher, a waitress. all right, here&#146;s her driver license, this oughta be good, she always lies about this. how old did she say she was?", "answer": " she told me she was 25.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " oh, i almost don&#146;t want to show this.  just remember i&#146;m a minute younger.", "answer": " i am so stupid. of course she was lying! she&#146;s not a teacher. there&#146;s not such a thing as the top secret elementary school for the children of spies.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " no. you&#146;re not, you&#146;re not stupid.", "answer": " i&#146;m not smart.  i just wanted so much to&#133;be impulsive once. to be romantic.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " that&#146;s good, you should be impulsive and you should be romantic. just&#133;you did it with the wrong person.  what?", "answer": " it&#146;s just so weird, two people look so much alike, and so different.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": "  eric!! let&#146;s go!!", "answer": " i&#146;d better go, deal&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey! well, i had to give the kid fifty bucks to stop crying.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " that&#146;s not so bad.", "answer": " no, i also had to go to a couple houses with him as his girlfriend. oh, i am just awful with children!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " come on! you&#146;re good with kids. they&#146;re just crazy on halloween. y&#146;know, they&#146;re all greedy and hopped up on sugar!", "answer": " really? you think that&#146;s all it is?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " look, i wanted to tell i&#146;m-i&#146;m sorry you lost.", "answer": " listen, i&#146;ve got a secret for ya. i let him win.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": "  is that a secret or a lie.", "answer": " no, i let him win&#151;ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " would you tell her i let you win please?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": " chandler please!", "answer": " oh what&#146;s the matter? are you scared?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}]